U.S. President's Railroad Commission Photographs 5003 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XIV: Louisville and Nashville Railroad (L&N): Birmingham Division, yards, passenger terminals, and industries
  - View of the Seaboard Railroad Yard, Looking South, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - L&N Tote Track at Boyles Yard, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 68)
    On the right is a power line pole creating very close clearance. To the left of photo is a stock unloading pen creating very close clearance. Notice the tall grass along track. This track is a dead end track with a platform build at the end to load and unload trailers.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Southern Train Crossing the L&N Main Line at 30th Street, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 69)
    The Engine is approaching the terminal station. SOU Unit 6911.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - Southern Train Crossing the L&N Main Line at 30th Street, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - L&N Yard Switchers 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 71)
    This is the type of engine used in switching and road service at Bessemer Yard.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - L&N Yard Switchers 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Two Unit L&N Engine, Backing Up the Main Line at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 73)
    View from L&N Units 426 and 429. Sequence of photographs with O-26, O-27, O-28, O-29, O-30, O-31, O-32. On the left are two L&N engines coupled together. The engine just back of the L&N engine in the center is a Southern R.R. yard engine, approaching the L&N track from the left side of each engine. Only the fireman on the L&N units can observe the approach of the Southern R.R. engine. Only the fireman on the Southern engine can see the L&N engine. Notice the road alongside of the engine, and the grass and weeds. School children use this road as a short cut to school and there is no protection at the crossing.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - Two Unit L&N Engine, Backing Up the Main Line at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 75)
    The engine are on the main line going North. By the brakeman is a switch leading around a "Y" and the south main line to Tuscaloosa. This switch is to be lined and lock as last used. Note the engines are backing up and signal is being passed on fireman side. View of L&N Units 426 and 429. Sequence of photographs with O-26, O-27, O-28, O-29, O-30, O-31, O-32.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 77)
    There are five tracks in right of picture. The lead curves to the right. This yard is very descending toward the engine. Derails in the tracks. Notice the fireman in a position to see if rails are off, also to watch car to see if they roll out as well as take signal.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 79)
    The engine is shoving the cab around the lead. Brakeman waiting at switch to head engine around "Y". Signals are being passed on left side of engine.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - South End of the L&N Yard at Bessemer, L&N Units 426 and 429, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 80)
    The engine is on the No. 2 track, in the south end of Bessemer Yard. Notice the grass and debris along track.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - L&N Units 426 and 429 with Cars Sitting on the South Leg of the "Y" at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 81)
    The track make a sharp turn to the left. Notice the Brakeman next to car passing signal on left side. Also the tall grass along track just ahead of engine is a rail road crossing also a motor car house where section men keep their tools and automobiles.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - L&N Units 426 and 429 with Cars Sitting on the South Leg of the "Y" at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 82)
    Sequence with O-26, O-27, O-28, O-29, O-31, O-32. The curve of the track is still on the fireman's side. The engine has just pulled out of the yard shown in photo O-28. All the signals are passed on the left or fireman's side of the engine. The grass and weeds on the track and in front of the engine makes the wheels slide when the brake is applied very hard. It is hazardous switching on track like this.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - L&N Units 426 and 429 with Cars Sitting on the South Leg of the "Y" at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - L&N Units 426 and 429 with Cars Further Around "Y" at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 84)
    Sequence with O-26, O-27, O-28, O-29, O-31, O-32. The stop board just in front of the engine is the Southern R.R. track, where the Southern engine was in O-26. The houses at the let of the photo are the motor car house and tool shop for the track men. Because of the track curvature to the left only the fireman can see if a moor car or track men are on the track. All the signals are passed on the left side. The engineer has to rely on the fireman to see if the track is clear.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - L&N Units 426 and 429 with Cars Further Around "Y" at Bessemer, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 85)
    Sequence with O-26, O-27, O-28, O-29, O-31, O-32. The engine has advanced just a little further along the rack. The engine at the top of the photo is entering a very heavily traveled street crossing, 19th Street. Notice the building at the top left corner of the picture. It blocks the motorists' view of the engine on the track. Due to the curvature of the track the engineer cannot see the street until the engine has entered the street crossing. There is also a main line switch in front of the house. The fireman is the only one who can see the switch and the crossing. The engineer operates in the blind, depending completely on the fireman for instructions. In this sequence of photos there are two GP7 hooded type engines coupled together.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - Seaboard Track Looking North from 10th Avenue North, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 86)
    This is a view of the Seaboard Railroad track at 10th Avenue and 30th Street North, Birmingham, Alabama. Notice the insufficient clearance sign at the right side of the photo and also the trees and bushes where the box car is spotted in the upper left center. The grass along the track is very hazardous for the ground crew getting on and off the moving cars. At the upper corner left of the photo is 28th Street which is heavily traveled by trucks and autos. Also notice the stop sign at the left of the picture where in addition to the street crossing, there is also a railroad crossing. It is essential to have a fireman here to pass signals and observe the crossing.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - View from Fireman's Side of Locomotive While Pushing Flat Car and Gondola Through Nashville Bridge Plant, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 152)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 58, Folder 152)
- Series XV: Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (The Milwaukee Road): locomotives and rolling stock
  This series consists of photographs of the some of the Milwaukee Road's locomotives and rolling stock. These photographs were not submitted to the Commission and as such do not have identifying exhibit numbers. This series documents piggy-backing operations in automobile lots as well as Milwaukee Road engines and flat cars. The location of these photographs is unknown. The Milwaukee Road was a class I railroad that operated in the Midwest and Northwest of the United States from 1847 until 1980. It is possible that these photographs were taken in either Minneapolis or Seattle as part of photographing Great Northern Railway facilities.
  - Milwaukee Railroad Flat Car with Semi Truck Auto Carrier (Box 53, Folder 156)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 156)
  - Auto Trailers on Milwaukee Road Flat Cars (Box 53, Folder 157)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 157)
  - Loading Auto Trailer on Milwaukee Road Flat Cars (Box 53, Folder 158)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 158)
  - Loading Auto Trailers on Milwaukee Road Flat Cars (Box 53, Folder 159)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 159)
  - Car Lot with Auto Trailer on Milwaukee Road Flat Cars (Box 53, Folder 160)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 160)
  - Car Lot with Auto Trailer on Milwaukee Road Flat Cars (Box 53, Folder 161)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 161)
  - View from Engineer's Side of Cab (Box 53, Folder 162)
    View of auto trailers on Milwaukee Road flat cars.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 162)
  - Milwaukee Road Locomotives 299 and 286 (Box 53, Folder 194)
    No. 299, EMD GP9; No. 286, EMD GP9
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 194)
  - The Milwaukee Road Units 299 and 286 (Box 61, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 61, Folder 76)
- Series XVI: New York Central Railroad (NYCRR) Cleveland Division Collinwood Yards
  This series consists of photographs of the New York Central Railroad's facilities in Cleveland, Ohio. These photographs were not submitted to the Commission as exhibits, but were mounted on cardboard and drawn on to highlight certain features of the Collinwood Yards. Collinwood Yards was one of the principal repair facilities and freight transfer points of the NYCRR. It included a brick roundhouse, built to house and repair locomotives; a machine shop, housing an engine room; a blacksmith shop; and an office constructed with upstairs apartments for the road's employees. The yards, situated along present-day E. 152nd St. just south of the Lakeland Freeway, were expanded in 1903 and again in 1929; at that time they included 120 miles of track and could handle 2,000 cars daily. In 1933 the facilities employed about 2,000 workers. By the end of World War II, the Collinwood Yards became a major switching and diesel repair facility for the NYCRR and later for the Penn Central Transportation Company.
  - New York Central Unit 5807 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Manufacturer: EMD Model: GP7
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - New York Central Unit 896 (1 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 105)
    Part of set of two mounted boards.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 105)
  - New York Central Unit 896 (2 of 2) (Box 62, Folder 106)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 106)
  - New York Central Unit 896 (Box 62, Folder 107)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 107)
  - Railroad Track Construction (Box 62, Folder 108)
    .
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 108)
  - Railroad Yard with Freight Cars, Passenger Cars and Gondolas (Box 62, Folder 109)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 109)
  - Railroad Track Construction (Box 62, Folder 110)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 110)
  - Passenger Cars and Highlighted Track in Foreground (Box 62, Folder 111)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 111)
  - Passenger Cars and Railroad Tracks, With Highlighted Tracks on Right (Box 62, Folder 112)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 112)
  - Passenger Cars and Railroad Tracks (Box 62, Folder 113)
    CLC Cleveland, OH.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 113)
  - Railway Turntable (Box 62, Folder 114)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 114)
  - Freight Cars and Tank Cars in Railroad Yard (Box 62, Folder 115)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 115)
  - Railway Turntable (Box 62, Folder 116)
    Annotation on photograph: "West from 152nd Street Bridge. Cleve. O. C.L.C." with a hand-drawn compass rose.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 116)
  - Freight Cars, Tank Cars and Hopper Cars in Yard With Highlighted Tracks in Background (Box 62, Folder 117)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 62, Folder 117)
- Series XVII: Northern Pacific Railroad and Great Northern Railway: facilities in Spokane, Washington
  This series consists of photographs of facilities in Spokane, Washington used by both the Northern Pacific Railroad and Great Northern Railway. These photographs were not submitted to the Commission and as such do not have identifying exhibit numbers. The photographs in this series are arranged as a group because of their location and because the NP and the GN co-owned the Spokane, Portland & Seattle Railway (SP&S). The SP&S was a joint venture between the two railroads, both controlled by James J. Hill, to build a railroad along the north bank of the Columbia River, connecting the two transcontinental railroads to Portland, Oregon from Spokane, Washington. The SP&S served the new industries located along the river, including aluminum plants, sawmills, chemical factories and grain elevators. The photographs in this series depict industries in and around Spokane, the car end engine shops of the NP, and the Great Northern Train Station with its iconic clock tower which is the only part of the building that remains standing today.
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 99)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 99)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 100)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 100)
  - Freight Yard (Box 53, Folder 101)
    Engine 405 in foreground
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 101)
  - Elevator With Storage Silos (Box 53, Folder 102)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 102)
  - Elevator With Storage Silos (Box 53, Folder 103)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 103)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 104)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 104)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 105)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 105)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 106)
    NP Locomotive 405
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 106)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 107)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 107)
  - Freight Yard, Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 108)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 108)
  - Freight Yard, Grade Crossing (Box 53, Folder 109)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 109)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 110)
    Note snow plow to right and caboose storage track. Grain storage silos and elevator in background of picture.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 110)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 111)
    Caboose storage track, turn table, and snow plows.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 111)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 112)
    Note the snow plow more toward the left of the photograph. Turn table to right. Rotary Snow Plow Engine No. 42; NP Caboose 35. NP Unit 415.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 112)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 113)
    Rotary Snow Plow Engine No. 42.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 113)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 114)
    Turn table and car shops.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 114)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 115)
    Different perspective than previous pictures of same facilities. NP Unit 415, turntable, and car shops.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 115)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 116)
    Slightly different perspective of photo, compared to previous ones. Rotary No. 42 and wedge snow plow, turntable, and car shops.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 116)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 117)
    Note spare rail on right side of photo.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 117)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 118)
    Note the spare rail on right side of photo.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 118)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 119)
    Continued panorama of NP facilities. Car shop and tracks to turntable.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 119)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 53, Folder 120)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 120)
  - Grain Elevator With Storage Silos (Box 53, Folder 129)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 129)
  - Great Northern Passenger Train Freight Yard, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 143)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 143)
  - Great Northern Train Freight Yard, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 144)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 144)
  - Great Northern Passenger Train Freight Yard, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 145)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 145)
  - Armour Plant Stock Pens, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 146)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 146)
  - Gates Crossing the Track at Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 147)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 147)
  - Gates Crossing the Track at Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 148)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 148)
  - Armour Plant Stock Pens (Box 53, Folder 149)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 149)
  - Track Geometry for Industrial Siding at Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 150)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 150)
  - Track Geometry for Industrial Siding at Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 151)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 151)
  - Track Geometry for Industrial Siding at Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 152)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 152)
  - Back of Armour Plant (Box 53, Folder 153)
    Railroad tracks in foreground.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 153)
  - Calf in a Crate (Box 53, Folder 154)
    Possibly in a freight car.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 154)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 164)
    Note the freight station to the left.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 164)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 165)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 165)
  - Great Northern Depot, Freight Yard, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 166)
    Grade crossing next to loading platforms.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 166)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 167)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 167)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 168)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 168)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 169)
    Note the Freight Station to the left.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 169)
  - Great Northern Depot and Clock Tower, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 170)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 170)
  - Great Northern Depot, Siding and Team Track, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 171)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 171)
  - Great Northern Grade Crossing in Freight Yard, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 172)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 172)
  - Great Northern Grade Crossing in Freight Yard, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 173)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 173)
  - Industrial Siding, Grain Elevator, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 174)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 174)
  - Industrial Siding to Grain Elevator, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 175)
    Note grain elevator in the background (same as previous photo).
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 175)
  - Industrial Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 176)
    Store: Massey Ferguson
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 176)
  - Industrial Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 177)
    Store: Knopp Taxidermy
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 177)
  - Industrial Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 178)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 178)
  - Grade Crossing and Industy Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 179)
    Hygrade Meat Plant
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 179)
  - Grade Crossing and Industry Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 180)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 180)
  - Grade Crossing and Industry Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 181)
    Sign for "Dix Steel"
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 181)
  - Grade Crossing and Industry Siding, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 182)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 182)
  - Great Northern Freight Yard Locomotive No. 2, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 185)
    GN Unit 2. ALCO S2.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 185)
  - Great Northern Freight Yard Locomotive No. 2, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 186)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 186)
  - Spokane Freight Yard, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 197)
    Yard Engine No. 407. Maker: EMD Model: GP9
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 53, Folder 197)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 38)
    Different perspective of yard.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 40)
    Note turntable to right in mid-ground.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 41)
    Note snow plow to right and Caboose storage track.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 46)
    Note turntable to the right and snow plow to the left.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 47)
    Slightly different perspective from previous picture. Snow plow to the left, turntable to the right.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Northern Pacific Railroad and Engine Facility (Box 57, Folder 48)
    Note snow plow to left and turntable to right mid-ground.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Grain Elevator With Storage Silos (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - Grade Crossing and Industry Siding (Box 57, Folder 50)
    Silos in Background.
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Grade Crossing and Industry Siding (Box 57, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 57, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 57, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - Grade Crossing (Box 57, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - Freight Yard, Grade Crossing (Box 57, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 55)
  - Freight Yard, Grade Crossing (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Click for Image (Box 57, Folder 56)